A Finding Aid to the C. J. (Clarence Joseph) Bulliet Papers, circa 1888-1959, in the Archives of American Art AAA.bullclar
Archives of American Art
- Artist Files, 1919-1952; Series 4; 20 Linear feet Boxes 5-24
  - Wiles, Irving R., circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 73)
  - Wilford, Loran F., circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 74)
  - Wilhelmson, Carl, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 75)
  - Wilmovsky, Charles A., 1928-1937 (Box 24, Folder 76)
  - Willi, Jaeckel, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 77)
  - Williams, C. Warner, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 78)
  - Williams, Charles Sneed, 1936 (Box 24, Folder 79)
  - Williams, Edward K., circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 80)
  - Williams, Esther, 1938 (Box 24, Folder 81)
  - Williams, Florence White, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 82)
  - Williams, Frederick Ballard, 1929 (Box 24, Folder 83)
  - Williams, J. Scott, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 84)
  - Williams, Larry, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 85)
  - Williams, Walter R., circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 86)
  - Williams, Wheeler, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 87)
  - Williamson, Ada C., circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 88)
  - Williamson, H., circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 89)
  - Wilott, A., circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 90)
  - Wilson, Richard, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 91)
  - Wilt, Richard H., 1951 (Box 24, Folder 92)
  - Wiltz, Arnold, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 93)
  - Winholtz, Caleb, 1928 (Box 24, Folder 94)
  - Winn, Alice Collingbourne, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 95)
  - Winter, Charles Allan, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 96)
  - Winter, Ezra, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 97)
  - Wirksz-Kowalski, A., circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 98)
  - Wishart, Marie Ellen, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 99)
  - Witherstine, Donald F., 1934 (Box 24, Folder 100)
  - Witten, Thomas, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 101)
  - Wittenber, Jan, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 102)
  - Witter, Ella M., circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 103)
  - Wittrim, Albert, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 104)
  - Wittrup, John S., circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 105)
  - Woberil, Peter P., 1928 (Box 24, Folder 106)
  - Woeltz, Russell, 1938 (Box 24, Folder 107)
  - Wolchonok, Louis, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 108)
  - Wolf, Peggy, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 109)
  - Wolfe, Jack, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 110)
  - Wolff, Robert J., 1934 (Box 24, Folder 111)
  - Wollaston, John, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 112)
  - Wollheim, Gert, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 113)
  - Wood, Grant, 1933-1942 (Box 24, Folder 114)
  - Wood, Stanley, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 115)
  - Wood, Thelma, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 116)
  - Woodall, George, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 117)
  - Woodbury, C. O., 1928 (Box 24, Folder 118)
  - Woodforde, Samuel, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 119)
  - Woodruff, Hale A., circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 120)
  - Woodruff, Louise Lentz, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 121)
  - Woods, Beatrice, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 122)
  - Woodward, Robert, 1931 (Box 24, Folder 123)
  - Woodward, Stanley, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 124)
  - Woolsey, Carl, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 125)
  - Woolsey, Wood, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 126)
  - Worcester, Albert, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 127)
  - Wormser, Lucie, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 128)
  - Wouters, Rik, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 129)
  - Wright, Frank Lloyd, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 130)
  - Wright, James, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 131)
  - Wright, Marsham E., 1927 (Box 24, Folder 132)
  - Wright, Norman B., 1937-1939 (Box 24, Folder 133)
  - Wright, R. Stevens, 1935 (Box 24, Folder 134)
  - Wuermer, Carl, 1929 (Box 24, Folder 135)
  - Wyant, A. H., circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 136)
  - Wydra, Jan, 1930 (Box 24, Folder 137)
  - Wyeth, Andrew, 1948 (Box 24, Folder 138)
  - Wyeth, N. C., circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 139)
  - Yacoe, Don, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 140)
  - Yago, Rafael, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 141)
  - Yarrow, William, 1941 (Box 24, Folder 142)
  - Yarushalmy, David, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 143)
  - Yates, Cullen, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 144)
  - Yefanov, Vasily, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 145)
  - Yeishi, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 146)
  - Yonan, Solomon D., circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 147)
  - Yoshida, Asaji, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 148)
  - Yoshida, Hiroshi, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 149)
  - Young, Arthur R., circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 150)
  - Young, C. Jac, 1931 (Box 24, Folder 151)
  - Young, J., circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 152)
  - Young, Mahonri, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 153)
  - Young, Richard Carr, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 154)
  - Younghunter, John, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 155)
  - Zadkine, Ossip, 1931-1942 (Box 24, Folder 156)
  - Zak, Eugene, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 157)
  - Zaratheutia, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 158)
  - Zarraga, Angel, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 159)
  - Zerbe, Karl, 1948 (Box 24, Folder 160)
  - Zettler, Emil R., circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 161)
  - Ziegler, Henry, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 162)
  - Ziem, Felix, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 163)
  - Zilzer, Gyula, 1936 (Box 24, Folder 164)
  - Zimm, Bruno, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 165)
  - Zirdi, Angelo, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 166)
  - Ziroli, Nicola, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 167)
  - Zoffany, Johann, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 168)
  - Zoir, Emile, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 169)
  - Zorach, Marguerite, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 170)
  - Zorach, William, 1932-1939 (Box 24, Folder 171)
  - Zorn, Anders, 1935 (Box 24, Folder 172)
  - Zubiaurre, Ramon de, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 173)
  - Zubiaurre, Valentin de, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 174)
  - Zuccarelli, Francesco, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 175)
  - Zuccherro, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 176)
  - Zuloaga, Ignacio, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 177)
  - Zulow, Franz, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 178)
  - Zurburan, Francisco de, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 179)
  - Unidentified Artists - Decorative Arts, 1930 (Box 24, Folder 180)
  - Unidentified Artists - Paintings, 1929 (Box 24, Folder 181)
  - Unidentified Artists - Prints and Drawings, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 182)
  - Unidentified Artists - Sculpture, circa 1888-1959 (Box 24, Folder 183)
- Subject Files, 1909-1952; Series 5; 2.3 Linear feet Boxes 25-27
  Subject files concerning topics that interested Bulliet consist mainly of photographs and printed material, with a small amount of correspondence. These were housed at Rockford College for a number of years, and many items were stamped "Rockford College Archives."
  - Arthur Ackermann and Son, Inc., circa 1888-1959 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Adler Planetarium, circa 1888-1959 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - African Art, 1934-1935 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Ahi Ezer Congregation, circa 1888-1959 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Albright Art Gallery, "British Contemporary Painting Exhibition", 1945 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - American Abstract Artists, circa 1888-1959 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - American Artists' Congress, 1936-1937 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - American Folk Art Gallery, "An American In Paris" Exhibition, circa 1888-1959 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - American Indian Art, circa 1888-1959 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Ancient Art, 1928 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Art In War, 1939-1942 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Art Institute of Chicago (Box 25)
    - General, 1936-1951 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Annual Exhibitions by Artists of Chicago and Vicinity, 1939-1941 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - "58th Annual Exhibition of American Painting and Sculpture: Abstract and Surrealist Art", 1947 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - "56 Paintings by Hogarth, Constable, and Turner" Exhibition, 1946 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - "Masterpieces of Art from Vienna" Exhibition, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - "Masterpieces of French Art", 1941 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - "Twentieth Century Art from the Louise and Walter Arensberg Collection" Exhibition, 1949 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Artists Guild of Chicago, 1946-1949 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Artists List, Unidentified Exhibition, circa 1888-1959 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - "Artists of Chicago Past and Present" Exhibitions, 1935 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Artists Organizations in Chicago, circa 1888-1959 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Artists Union of Chicago, 1936-1939 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Arts and Crafts Club of New Orleans, 1924 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Arts Club of Chicago, 1936-1940 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Arts Council, "Exhibition of 100 Paintings", circa 1888-1959 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Austin, Oak Park and River Forest Art League, 1932 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Barnes Foundation, 1927-1942 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Bather, Atlantic City, 1922 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Beloit College, Theodore Lyman Wright Art Hall, circa 1888-1959 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Bernhardt, Sarah, circa 1888-1959 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Bohemia, 1940 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Boswell, Peyton, 1936-1939 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Breckenridge Summer School of Art, 1925 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Brooklyn-Paramount Theatre Art Collection, circa 1888-1959 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Buddhist Art, circa 1888-1959 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Bullit, William Christian, 1939 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Burr, Jane, 1922 (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Carnegie Institute (Box 25)
    - General, 1938-1947 (Box 25, Folder 39)
    - "Painting in the United States, 1948" Exhibition (Box 25, Folder 40)
    - "27th International Exhibition," Jury of Award and Committee of Selection (oversize, see Box 37), 1928 (Box 25, Folder 41)
      Oversized material housed in Box 37
  - Carpenter, Mrs. J. Alden, circa 1888-1959 (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - Carson Pirie Scott and Company Gallery, circa 1888-1959 (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - "Century of Progress Souvenir Exhibition", circa 1888-1959 (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - Chicago, circa 1888-1959 (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - Chicago Civic Opera House, "Ballet in Art Since 1900" Exhibition, circa 1888-1959 (Box 25, Folder 46)
  - Chicago Galleries Association, circa 1888-1959 (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - Chicago Natural History Museum/Field Museum of Natural History, 1952 (Box 25, Folder 48)
  - Chicago No-Jury Society of Artists, Inc., 1936-1947 (Box 25, Folder 49)
  - Chicago Public Library, 1944-1952 (Box 25, Folder 50)
  - Chinese Art, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 51)
  - Christian Art, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 52)
  - Chrysler Collection, 1941 (Box 25, Folder 53)
  - Claremont Colleges, Graduate Institute of Art, 1931-1950 (Box 25, Folder 54)
  - Comet Engraving Company, circa 1888-1959 (Box 25, Folder 55)
  - Commission for the Encouragement of Local Art, Chicago, 1915-1925 (Box 25, Folder 56)
  - Communism/"Reds", 1940-1952 (Box 25, Folder 57)
  - Cornell, Regina, 1909 (Box 25, Folder 58)
  - Craven, Thomas, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 59)
  - Crimes, 1935-1952 (Box 25, Folder 60)
  - Crocker Art Gallery, "Three Centuries of Landscape Drawing" Exhibition, 1940 (Box 25, Folder 61)
  - Dana, John Cotton, 1929 (Box 25, Folder 62)
  - Donarey, A. V., 1922 (Box 25, Folder 63)
  - Downtown Gallery (Daylight Gallery and American Folk Art Gallery), circa 1888-1959 (Box 25, Folder 64)
  - Easter Island Art and Artifacts (A. J. Morlin Collection), circa 1888-1959 (Box 25, Folder 65)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight, 1952 (Box 25, Folder 66)
  - Enright, Richard, circa 1888-1959 (Box 25, Folder 67)
  - Egyptian Art, circa 1888-1959 (Box 25, Folder 68)
  - Encyclopedia Britannica Collection, 1941 (Box 25, Folder 69)
  - Fair Store Mural, Oak Park, Ill., circa 1888-1959 (Box 25, Folder 70)
  - Fairmount Park Art Association, "Third Sculpture International" Exhibition, 1949 (Box 25, Folder 71)
  - Folk Art, 1931-1937 (Box 25, Folder 72)
  - Friends of American Art, Chicago, 1916 (Box 25, Folder 73)
  - Gallery of the United States (Venice, Italy), circa 1888-1959 (Box 25, Folder 74)
  - Goldblatt, Maurice H. (concerning Mona Lisa), 1927 (Box 25, Folder 75)
  - Grand Central Art Galleries, circa 1888-1959 (Box 25, Folder 76)
  - Great Art Derby, 1938-1939 (Box 25, Folder 77)
  - Greek Sculpture, 1927 (Box 25, Folder 78)
  - "Guernica" (Pictura Films), 1951 (Box 25, Folder 79)
  - Harding Museum, circa 1888-1959 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Haueveer, Armand, 1932 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Headland, Helen, circa 1888-1959 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Highland Park Art Gallery, Dallas, circa 1888-1959 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Hitler, Adolf, 1940-1945 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Hollywood, 1933-1952 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Hoover, Herbert, 1932-1952 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Hull-House Art Center, 1942 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Illinois State Fair (Box 26)
    - Exhibition, circa 1888-1959 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - "Old Northwest Territory Art Exhibit", 1947-1948 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Index of American Design, 1936-1937 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Indian Art, 1928 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Indians of North America, 1927-1932 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Institute of Contemporary Art, Boston, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - International Association of Art Critics, 1949-1952 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Japanese Art, circa 1888-1959 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Jeritza, Maria, 1946 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Jewish Art, 1936-1942 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Chester H. Johnson Galleries, circa 1888-1959 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Johnson, Mrs. Edwin H., circa 1888-1959 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Kizer, Edan Wright, 1938 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Kress Collection, National Gallery of Art, 1939 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Lamarr, Hedy, 1940-1941 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Lamour, Dorothy, circa 1888-1959 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Larer, James, circa 1888-1959 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Lawrence, Georgie, circa 1888-1959 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Gertrude Lawrence Collection, circa 1888-1959 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Lincoln, Abraham, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - "Little Egypt", 1951 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - London, 1951 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Lupino, Ida, 1940-1944 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Lynching, circa 1888-1959 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Magnificent Mile Art Festival, 1951-1952 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Maguire, Mary, circa 1888-1959 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Main Street Gallery, 1951-1952 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Mantell, Robert B., 1920 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Mascagni, Pietro, circa 1888-1959 (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Master Building (Roerich Museum, Master Institute of United Arts, and Corona Mundi International Art Center), circa 1888-1959 (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - McCarthy, Joseph, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - McCauley, Lena M., 1921-1929 (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - McCormick, Chauncey, 1937 (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - McCray, Warren T., circa 1888-1959 (Box 26, Folder 42)
  - Meier-Graefe, Julius, circa 1888-1959 (Box 26, Folder 43)
  - Michigan Boulevard Association Emblem Contest, circa 1888-1959 (Box 26, Folder 44)
  - Midwestern Conference of Artists Unions and Organizations, 1936 (Box 26, Folder 45)
  - Minneapolis Institute of Arts, circa 1888-1959 (Box 26, Folder 46)
  - Minter, Mary Miles, 1940 (Box 26, Folder 47)
  - Mountain Lake Sanctuary, 1934 (Box 26, Folder 48)
  - Municipal Art Committee, New York, 1937 (Box 26, Folder 49)
  - Music Criticism, circa 1888-1959 (Box 26, Folder 50)
  - Museum of Modern Art (Box 26)
    - "Exhibition of Contemporary North American Painting", circa 1888-1959 (Box 26, Folder 51)
    - "Soviet Children's Art" Exhibition, circa 1888-1959 (Box 26, Folder 52)
  - Natchitoches Art Colony, circa 1888-1959 (Box 26, Folder 53)
  - Nazis, 1941-1952 (Box 26, Folder 54)
  - Negro Art, 1935 (Box 26, Folder 55)
  - Negroes, circa 1888-1959 (Box 26, Folder 56)
  - Neoterics, circa 1888-1959 (Box 26, Folder 57)
  - New Oriental Theater, circa 1888-1959 (Box 26, Folder 58)
  - New York City, circa 1888-1959 (Box 26, Folder 59)
  - New York World's Fair, 1939 (Box 26, Folder 60)
  - Newark Museum, 1929 (Box 26, Folder 61)
  - North Shore Art League, circa 1888-1959 (Box 26, Folder 62)
  - Omaha Society of Fine Arts, circa 1888-1959 (Box 26, Folder 63)
  - Outdoor Chicago Art Fair, 1932 (Box 26, Folder 64)
  - Robert Dale Owen Collection, circa 1888-1959 (Box 26, Folder 65)
  - Palette and Chisel Club, circa 1888-1959 (Box 26, Folder 66)
  - Persian Art, 1931-1939 (Box 26, Folder 67)
  - Philadelphia Museum of Art, circa 1888-1959 (Box 26, Folder 68)
  - Political Institute, Leaders of the Debate, 1922 (Box 26, Folder 69)
  - Politics, 1945-1952 (Box 26, Folder 70)
  - Pomerene, Atlee, 1922 (Box 26, Folder 71)
  - Pre-Historic Art, 1926 (Box 26, Folder 72)
  - Primitive Art, North America, 1928-1930 (Box 26, Folder 73)
  - Radical Art, 1949 (Box 26, Folder 74)
  - Red Cross Drive, circa 1888-1959 (Box 26, Folder 75)
  - "Redlap" (country home of Cyril Mande), circa 1888-1959 (Box 26, Folder 76)
  - Religion, 1944-1951 (Box 26, Folder 77)
  - Riccardo Studio Restaurant, circa 1888-1959 (Box 26, Folder 78)
  - Robin, Sophie (Sophie Robin Nussbaum), circa 1888-1959 (Box 26, Folder 79)
  - Roman Art, circa 1888-1959 (Box 26, Folder 80)
  - Romance, 1936-1952 (Box 26, Folder 81)
  - Royalty, 1936-1952 (Box 26, Folder 82)
  - Russian Art, circa 1888-1959 (Box 26, Folder 83)
  - "Satira" (Patricia Schmidt), 1946-1950 (Box 26, Folder 84)
  - Scholastic Art Exhibition for the Northeastern Illinois Area, 1950 (Box 26, Folder 85)
  - School in Rural California, circa 1888-1959 (Box 26, Folder 86)
  - School of Design in Chicago/Institute of Design, 1937-1946 (Box 26, Folder 87)
  - Schoop, Trudi, 1936 (Box 26, Folder 88)
  - Schumacher, William E., 1931 (Box 26, Folder 89)
  - Sidis, William James, 1944 (Box 26, Folder 90)
  - Silver, Carol, 1943-1944 (Box 26, Folder 91)
  - Simpson, Wallis Warfield, 1936 (Box 26, Folder 92)
  - Society for Sanity In Art, Inc., 1938 (Box 26, Folder 93)
  - Society of Independent Artists Exhibition, 1928 (Box 26, Folder 94)
  - A. G. Spaulding and Bros., circa 1888-1959 (Box 26, Folder 95)
  - South Side Community Art Center, 1944-1946 (Box 26, Folder 96)
  - Southern Printmakers Society, 1939 (Box 26, Folder 97)
  - Southern States Art League, 1930 (Box 26, Folder 98)
  - Special Committee on Artists' Oil Paints, 1940 (Box 26, Folder 99)
  - Stevenson, Adlai and Wyatt Wilson, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 100)
  - Suffolk Galleries, 1930 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Swastikas, 1943 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Sweeney, James Johnson, 1924-1941 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Tapestries and Carpets, circa 1888-1959 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Tate Gallery, "Exhibition of 200 Years of American Painting", 1946 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Taylor Art School, circa 1888-1959 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Texas Continental Central Exposition, circa 1888-1959 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Tibetan Art, circa 1888-1959 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Tinney, Frank, 1940 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Tor House (home of Robinson Jeffers), circa 1888-1959 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Trotsky, Leon, 1940 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Truman, Harry, 1952 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Truman, Margaret, 1952 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Tykociner, Joseph T., 1922 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Unidentified Individuals, circa 1888-1959 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - University of Chicago, Renaissance Society, "English Drawings of the Eighteenth and Early Nineteenth Century" Exhibition", circa 1888-1959 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - University of Illinois (Box 27)
    - "Contemporary Art Exhibition" Jury, circa 1888-1959 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - "26th Faculty Art Exhibition", 1949 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Women, 1927-1952 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Women in Trousers, 1933-1941 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Wonderland Way Art Club, 1937 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Works Progress Administration, 1934-1941 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - World's Columbian Exposition (1893), Woman's Building, circa 1888-1959 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Zigrosser, Carl, circa 1888-1959 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Oversized "27th International Exhibition," Jury of Award and Committee of Selection, 1928 (Box 37)
    Oversized material from Box 25, F41
- Printed Material, 1909-1952; Series 6; 7.7 Linear feet Boxes 27-34, 36-37
  Printed material by Bulliet consists of newspaper articles and columns, books, and reviews of art, book, and music. Items produced by others include books, clippings, exhibition related items, museum and art school publications, periodicals, and press releases.
  Exhibition related items, arranged chronologically, are categorized as "Chicago" and "elsewhere." They consist of announcements and invitations, catalogs and checklists, and prospectuses. Museum publications (excluding exhibition catalogs, announcements, invitations, and prospectuses) are arranged alphabetically by name of institution and include brochures, annual reports, and newsletters. Periodicals (excluding those issued by museums) are arranged alphabetically by title.
  Additional exhibition catalogs, clippings, and press releases are among the Artist Files and Subject Files, and a smaller number are attachments to Correspondence.
  The series is arranged as 2 subseries:
  6.1: Printed Material By Bulliet
  6.2: Printed Material By Others
  - Printed Material By Bulliet, 6.1
    - Articles/Columns (Box 27)
      - Miscellaneous, 1930-1952 (Box 27, Folder 25-35)
      - Chicago Evening Post Magazine of the Art World, 1924-1925; (1 volume) (Box 36)
      - Chicago Evening Post Magazine of the Art World, 1925-1930 (Box 36)
      - Chicagoan, 1931-1932; (1 volume) (Box 36)
    - Books (Box 27)
      - Apples and Madonnas (incomplete), 1930 (Box 27, Folder 36)
      - Art Masterpieces of the 1933 Worlds Fair, Exhibited at The Art Institute of Chicago (vols. 1 and 2) (Box 27, Folder 37)
      - Art Masterpieces of the 1934 World's Fair Exhibition at The Art Institute of Chicago (Box 27, Folder 38)
      - Art Treasures from Vienna (1950); Done In A Day - From the Columns of The Chicago Daily News (1942; includes a column by Bulliet), 1942-1950 (Box 27, Folder 39)
      - French Art from David to Matisse (1941); Masterpieces of Italian Art (1939); The Story of Lent in Art Masterpieces (1951), 1939-1951 (Box 27, Folder 40)
    - Reviews (Box 27)
      - Book Reviews, 1924-1952 (Box 27, Folder 41)
      - Dance Reviews, 1941-1952 (Box 27, Folder 42)
      - Film Reviews, 1940-1949 (Box 27, Folder 43)
      - Music Reviews, 1940-1951 (Box 27, Folder 44-47)
      - Theater Reviews, 1928-1951 (Box 27, Folder 48)
  - Printed Material by Others, 6.2
    - Art Schools (Box 28)
      - Archipenko Art School, 1951 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Art Association of Indianapolis, Indiana, John Herron Art Institute, 1911 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Art Institute of Chicago, 1924-1929 (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Art Students League, 1928-1932 (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - American Academy of Art, circa 1888-1959 (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Chicago Academy of Fine Arts, circa 1888-1959 (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Dayton Art Institute, 1924 (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - Jewish People's Institute, People's Art School, circa 1888-1959 (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - Lawrence College, Worcester Art Center, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 9)
      - Layton School of Art, 1927 (Box 28, Folder 10)
      - Mills College, 1934 (Box 28, Folder 11)
      - Minneapolis Society of Fine Arts, 1934 (Box 28, Folder 12)
      - National Academy of Design, circa 1888-1959 (Box 28, Folder 13)
      - New York School of Fine and Applied Art, 1925 (Box 28, Folder 14)
      - Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts, 1938-1950 (Box 28, Folder 15)
      - Portland Art Association, 1927-1934 (Box 28, Folder 16)
      - [Wellington J.] Reynolds Atelier, circa 1888-1959 (Box 28, Folder 17)
      - Ringling School of Art, circa 1888-1959 (Box 28, Folder 18)
      - School of Design in Chicago/Institute of Design, 1938-1949 (Box 28, Folder 20)
        - School for Art Studies, circa 1888-1959 (Box 28, Folder 19)
      - Studio for the Art in Painting (Maurice Sterne and George Grosz), 1932 (Box 28, Folder 21)
      - Weisenborn School of Modern Art, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Books (Box 28)